Christian Kuroki

Senior Software Engineer









A highly skilled Software Engineer with 25 years of experience in backend, frontend development and data processing. Solid knowledge of many programming languages, software tools and methodologies. Worked on projects in different areas from blockchain to data science. Strong problem-solving and mentoring skills. Perfectionist but humble, and a responsible team player.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

2019 - Present

Paxos

Senior fullstack software engineer cryptocoin and financial assets management services

- Go microservices backend. Kubernetes. Terraform. Docker. RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL. Vault. gRPC. ERC20. Solidity.
- React, Typescript, MobX frontend.
- Agile, scrum, github, Jira, Jenkins.

Lead Software Developer

2018 - 2019

Birtwell Consulting

Lead software developer for a Big data AI startup

- Big Data. Airflow. Golang. Spark. PostgreSQL. AWS. S3. Python.
- Go, Docker, Microservices, REST, Scalability.

Senior Software Engineer

2018 - 6 months project

Phishlabs

Software development of a micro services based email processing service for automatic detection of phishing threats. Refactoring a Python MVP to make a scalable production-ready solution

- Golang. Python. PostgreSQL, Docker, Office365. SMTP, rpc.
- Natural language processing, text search.

Fullstack developer, Data analyst

2016 - 2018

Jovio

Platform development for a real estate startup. Data collection, processing and transformation services and infrastructure. Data analytics.

- Go. REST API, PostgreSQL.Gecoding. React. Redux
- ELT. Big Data. Airflow, Spark. blockchain. ERC20

Fullstack Developer

2014 - 2016

Fullstack Labs

Fullstack developer for a software factory

 React, Redux, NodeJS, GraphSQL, Docker, PostgreSQL, RabbitMQ, Electron, React Native.

CTO - Software Engineer

2007 - 2014

Kombi Labs

Founder and CTO of a small boutique software factory working with many different companies, from banks to telcos in Latin America, USA and Europe

• Ruby on Rails, Python, Flask, C, NodeJS, EmberJS, Angular, React.

EDUCATION

Systems Analyst

JFKennedy University of Argentina 1999 - 2002

SKILLS

Technical

Golang, Python, Javscript

React, Redux, Node.js

Express, Electron, React Native

Flask, Ruby on Rails

PostgreSQL, Redis, ElasticSearch

Hadoop, Spark

C, Lua, MongoDB

API, Big Data, Docker, Microservices, AWS

Agile, Scalability, Tuning

Continuous Deployment (CD), REST, GraphQL, Algorithms

Continuous Integration (CI), Git, Unit testing, TDD

Design Patterns, Availability, Networking

Open Source, Configuration Management (CM), NoSQL

Artificial Intelligence, Security, OOP, Machine Learning

Deployment, Web services

Professional

Passionate

Effective communication

Team player

Strong problem solver

Good time management

Self motivated, self taught

Never stop learning

LANGUAGES

Founder - CTO

odilaci

1998 - 2007

Dbas

Database support company. Commercial PostgreSQL support since 1998 in Latin America. Founded this company and worked with many companies in Argentina, Latin America and USA. Customers: Telecom Argentina, Citi Bank, Banco Credicoop, Educ.ar, Metrogas, CTI (Claro), Tengo (Honduras), AT&T, Universidad de Chile.

• PostgreSQL, C, Unix, Oracle, PL/SQL, Java.

Database Team Leader

1996 - 1998

BASF AG

Regional Datawarehouse project member. Data extraction and mapping from SAP/R3. Data transport software development. Intranet development.

C Programmer

1994 - 1996

Accenture

Worked in multiple projects: CTI Movil - Mobile telecommunications, Credit Lyonnais - Bank, Telefonica - Telecommunications, YPF - Oil company

English (Professional)

Spanish (Native)

INTERESTS

Music

Furniture making

Homebrewing

Biking





